I received a package from FILF and there is a latex dress inside. So without further ado, I will unpack it.
As you can see, we have a lot of zippers.
And I can already tell you that it's really heavy with all the zippers.
Really excited to try it on now.
Okay, it already fits, but it's not shiny yet, which is quite normal for new latex.
you have to wash and shine it up a few times until the shine sticks to the latex so I'll get to work.
Okay
this is the dress and I have to take a look in the mirror now because I didn't try it on before
oh nice
I love the design with the zippers everywhere also the arms here on the back sides and it
looks like kind of sun rays like the sun would be here and the rays in this direction so it gives
a nice optical effect like some kind of draping I don't know now of course we can open the zippers
all of them it was quite handy actually to get inside the dress and put it on because
You can open the arms for example and slip in there really fast as well as...
Let me close them again because I prefer them closed. You can also open the one up here.
Maybe a bit more than what I just had, something like this.
You can also open the one down here as far as you're comfortable with.
But as I said for putting it on, perfect.
Now we can also open these of course like here of course you can see the bra here I'm
wearing now at the moment.
Of course I could like open all the zippers to the max and show a lot of skin but that
was not the idea here.
idea from a design point of view and a story point of view was to be like a bit revealing
and tease a bit but not be too plump and not be too like in your face so phil has kind of a story
idea behind the outfits which are like concerning the latex itself we have 0.45 millimeters latex
gaunt here which is a bit thicker than your average latex sheet and it's a bit more firm
so it's quite nice to wear it's not as stretchy but it doesn't have to be super stretchy because
we have kind of a loose fit and with all the zippers there is no way the whole dress can
stretch anyway filth is a company based in the netherlands they're quite new they just
launched a webshop and they just published their first collection I can show you a few more pieces
here so check them out I will put everything down in the description text thank you to Filt for
sending this dress along I totally love it I love the design and I am definitely going to wear it
to fetish party this year maybe also to goth event if it's not too cold or too warm because
this latex. Anyway, I hope you enjoyed the video. Leave a thumbs up, leave a comment and a thumbs up
and I will see you in the next video. Bye!